Saturday Morning Musical Club records, 1909-1971 (bulk 1920-1948)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Performance Records, 1909-1971
  - Artist Series, 1913-1971
    - Ossy Renardy (violinist). February 1, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Ballet Theatre (cancelled?). February 8, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Christopher Lynch (tenor). March 4, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Afro-Cuban Review (cancelled?). September 9-11, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. December 15, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - De Paur's Infantry Chorus. February 14, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Sanroma (pianist). February 24, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Ballet Theatre. February 28, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Pierre Bernac (baritone) and Francis Poulenc (composer-pianist). March 6, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Talley Beatty and Company in Tropicana. October 21, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. December 14, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - De Paur's Infantry Chorus. January 16, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Vivian Della Chiesa (soprano). February 5, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Whittemore and Lowe (duo-pianists). February 26, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Mary Garden (lecture). November 20, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. December 12, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Carl Palangi (basso cantante). February 7, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Jose Iturbi (pianist). February 11, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Jorge Bolet (pianist). April 3, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Stephan Hero (violinist). January 16, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Slavenska-Franklin Ballet, with Alexandra Danilova. February 27, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Katie Lee, her guitar and folk songs. March 25, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Jorge Bolet (pianist). April 13, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Guiomar Novaes (pianist) (cancelled). March 8, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Victoria de Los Angeles (soprano). March 13, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Patricia Benkman (pianist). March 18, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Jose Greco and his company of Spanish Dancers. March 31, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Vronsky and Babin (duo-pianists). January 6, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Societa Corelli (string ensemble). December 2, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Vronsky and Babin (duo-pianists). January 6, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. March 3, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - "Ali Baba and the Forty Thieves," Lesseli Marionettes. March 5, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Jose Greco and his Spanish Dance Company. March 19, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Leon Fleisher (pianist). January 26, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Arthur Fiedler and the Boston Pops Orchestra. January 26, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. February 24, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Witold Malcuzynski (pianist). March 9, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Lola Montes and her Spanish Dancers. March 19, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - De Paur Opera Gala. January 25, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Luboshutz and Nemenoff (duo-pianists). February 4, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. February 22, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Jose Greco and his company of Spanish Dancers. March 18, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia Woodwind Quintet. May 27, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Festival Quartet. January 21, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. January 27, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jorge Bolet (pianist). February 26, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Mattiwilda Dobbs (coloratura soprano). March 24, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - National Ballet of Canada. March 28, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Lois Brandwynne (pianist). January 15, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. February 20, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jose Greco and his company of Spanish Dancers. February 27, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Benno and Sylvia Rabinof (violin and piano duo). March 30, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Tong-Il Han (pianist). January 20, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jose Greco and his Spanish Ballet. March 1, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - "Rigoletto," New York Opera Festival (cancelled). March 3, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Robert Joffrey Theatre Ballet. November 13, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. February 23, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Jean-Leon Destine and his Haitian Dance Company (cancelled). February 6, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Tong-Il Han (pianist). March 2, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Whittemore and Lowe (duo-pianists). March 17, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco Operatic Quartet. January 13, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Jose Greco and his Spanish Ballet. February 26, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - John Browning (pianist). April 6, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo. February 24, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Ruth Page's Chicago Opera Ballet. January 22, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Whittemore and Lowe (duo-pianists). January 28, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Jose Greco and his Spanish Ballet. March 12, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Dame Judith Anderson in "Lady Macbeth," and Medea." February 2, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - "On a Clear Day You Can See Forever," tour company. January 13, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "Cabaret," tour company. November 7-8, 1969? (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "I Do! I do!" tour company. March 28, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - "Zorba," tour company. March 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Various. 1921-1962 (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - Armitage, Merle (for various agencies). 1922-1932 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Baman, Catharine. 1921-1922 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Behymer. L. E. 1917-1947 (Box 19, Folder 6-10)
    - Columbia Artists Management. 1949-1961 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Culbertson, Harry and Arthur. 1921-1929 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Healy, Frank W. 1929 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Legitimate Theatre Corporation of America. 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Morini, Albert. 1941-1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Morris, William. 1946-1960 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Wagner, Charles L. 1921-1937 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Series IV: Season ticket records, 1929-1963
  - Season Ticket Records. 1929/30-1939/40 (Box 20, Volume 1-6)
  - Season Ticket Records. 1941/42-1958 (Box 21, Volume 1-7)
  - Season Ticket Records. 1959/60-1962/63 (Box 22, Volume 1-4)